1
00:00:00,560 --> 00:00:04,140
嗨 Dan，我们完成设置了，你要检查看看吗？
Hey Dan, we finished the settings. Do you want to check it out?

2
00:00:04,140 --> 00:00:05,120
恩 很好
>> Oh, great.

3
00:00:05,120 --> 00:00:07,180
等等，这里这些是什么鬼？
>> Wait. What's with all this stuff right here?

4
00:00:07,180 --> 00:00:10,790
很高兴你问了。这些是用来演示
>> I'm glad you asked. All this stuff will help me demonstrate the

5
00:00:10,790 --> 00:00:13,150
implicit intents的作用的
power of implicit intents. Leveraging other

6
00:00:13,150 --> 00:00:15,080
借助其他APP来实现你的APP的功能
apps to get functionality for your app

7
00:00:15,080 --> 00:00:20,330
举个例子，如果你可以通过一个intent来扫描条形码，
for free. For example, why would you write a bar code scanning app,

8
00:00:20,330 --> 00:00:23,282
你干嘛还要自己编写一个扫描条形码的程序
when you can just launch an intent to do it for you. [SOUND].

9
00:00:23,282 --> 00:00:25,748
再例如你可以通过intent来照一张照片而不需要编写一个相机APP
>> Or a camera app, where you can just launch

10
00:00:25,748 --> 00:00:29,839
当然，也没有必要单独编写一个电话APP仅仅用来拨号
an intent to fire a photo. [SOUND] And of course, it would make no sense to

11
00:00:29,839 --> 00:00:34,181
你只需要调用一个intent就可以了
write a phone app just to dial a phone number, you would just call the intent.

12
00:00:34,181 --> 00:00:36,124
等 这个我要
>> Wait, I need that.

13
00:00:36,124 --> 00:00:40,280
所以不要做别人做过的事情，越懒的码农犯错越少
>> In other words, don't reinvent the wheel. Lazy programmers make fewer

14
00:00:40,280 --> 00:00:42,620
好了，现在我们来编写一个implicit intent吧
mistakes. Now, let's go implement an

15
00:00:42,620 --> 00:00:47,450
Raydo? Dan又变得implicit了
implicit intent. Raydo? Dan's being implicit again.

