1
00:00:00,340 --> 00:00:04,440
添加一个菜单选项来允许在地图上查看用户的偏好地址
Add a menu option to view the user's preferred location on a map. It

2
00:00:04,440 --> 00:00:09,410
你手机上的任何一个地图APP都有这个功能
will be handled by any maps app that's available on your device. If there

3
00:00:09,410 --> 00:00:13,240
如果手机上没有地图APP，那就优雅地避免程序崩溃
is no map app on your device, handle this case gracefully to avoid a

4
00:00:13,240 --> 00:00:15,620
你可能想要回顾一下
crash. You might want to recall that

5
00:00:15,620 --> 00:00:18,460
使用SharedPreferences来存储偏好地址
we use SharedPreferences to store the preferred location.

