1
00:00:00,390 --> 00:00:05,689
已经完成了。让我们来看看答案。在main activity的菜单排版文件里
Done already. Let's go to the solution. In the menu layout file for the main

2
00:00:05,689 --> 00:00:10,540
也叫做main.xml，添加一个菜单选项
activity, called main.xml, we add another menu item

3
00:00:10,540 --> 00:00:12,740
它总是会在溢出菜单里
that will always be in the overflow menu.

4
00:00:14,010 --> 00:00:20,280
也要在string.xml里定义一个字符串。这个菜单要添加在
We also define the string in the strings.xml file. The menu will be inflated in

5
00:00:20,280 --> 00:00:22,770
main activity里。这样我们就可以操作
the main activity class, so we can handle

6
00:00:22,770 --> 00:00:25,550
这个新添加的菜单选项，通过调用
the map menu item being inflated. By calling

7
00:00:25,550 --> 00:00:28,230
一个叫openPreferredLocationInMap的协助函数
helper method called openPreferredLocationInMap

8
00:00:28,230 --> 00:00:31,650
这个协助函数从SharedPreferences
The helper method reads the users

9
00:00:31,650 --> 00:00:35,650
读取用户的偏好地址信息。然后
preferred location from SharedPreferences. Then we

10
00:00:35,650 --> 00:00:39,240
我们创建一个View Intent。把地址信息放进
create a view intent, indicating it's location

11
00:00:39,240 --> 00:00:44,460
它的数据URI。数据URI的格式可以在通用Intent的文档里找到
in the data URI. The format of the data URI was from the documentation

12
00:00:44,460 --> 00:00:49,150
你还可以添加一个邮编号码作为地址的查询参数
page on common intents. Where you can append a postal code as a query parameter.

13
00:00:50,490 --> 00:00:54,479
最后，我们用这个Intent做参数调用startActivity
Finally, we start an activity with [SOUND] this intent. Note

14
00:00:54,479 --> 00:00:58,560
注意，只有当这个Activity能被成功分解时，我们才开始这个Activity
that we only start the activity, if the activity resolves successfully.

